<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-31T12:22:11+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Phantom Cluster</title><author><name>Hitanshu Sahu</name></author><entry><title type="html">Ghost Recon Wildlands</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/01/30/Ghost-Recon-Game.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ghost Recon Wildlands" /><published>2019-01-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2019-01-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/30/Ghost-Recon-Game</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/01/30/Ghost-Recon-Game.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Clancy’s Ghost Recon Wildlands&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Developer(s)&lt;/strong&gt;	Ubisoft Paris
&lt;strong&gt;Publisher(s)&lt;/strong&gt;	Ubisoft&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform(s)&lt;/strong&gt;	Microsoft Windows,PlayStation 4,Xbox One
&lt;strong&gt;Genre(s)&lt;/strong&gt;	Tactical shooter&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tom Clancy’s Ghost Recon Wildlands is a tactical shooter video game developed by Ubisoft Paris and published by Ubisoft. It was released worldwide on March 7, 2017, for Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 4 and Xbox One, as the tenth installment in the Tom Clancy’s Ghost Recon franchise and is the first game in the Ghost Recon series to feature an open world environment. I am Playing this game in PS4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Little Story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game takes place in Bolivia in July 2019. The country has become increasingly unstable as a Mexican drug cartel known as the Santa Blanca Cartel gains more power and influence within the country and turns Bolivia into the world’s largest producer of cocaine. The United States government is compelled to act when a bomb targets the American embassy in La Paz and undercover DEA agent Ricardo “Ricky” Sandoval is executed by the cartel. A Ghost Recon fireteam is deployed to Bolivia as part of Operation Kingslayer, a joint operation between the CIA, DEA, and JSOC. The team consists of team leader and support gunner “Nomad”, vehicle and assault specialist “Midas”, hacker and tactical engineer “Holt”, and sniper “Weaver”. The Ghosts enter Bolivia with their CIA contact, Karen Bowman, who was also a close friend to Sandoval. They meet Pac Katari, leader of the Kataris 26, the only resistance against Santa Blanca. Pac Katari requests they rescue Amaru, whose ideologies inspired the Kataris 26, from Santa Blanca. The Ghosts are then free to tackle the cartel in any way and order they see fit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ghosts dismantle the cartel piece by piece, targeting their four main operations by attacking cocaine production facilities and stockpiles, disrupting smuggling operations, discrediting the cartel in the eyes of corrupt politicians and supporters, and inciting conflict between the cartel’s senior figures. After crippling a quarter of the cartel, the team are eventually contacted by the cartel’s leader, El Sueño, who lures them to a meeting and attempts to bribe the Ghosts into working for Santa Blanca. The Ghosts refuse his offer and instead tell him that his days are numbered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How the story ends depends on whether the Ghosts fully dismantled the cartel. If remnants of the cartel remain, Bowman will execute El Sueño, leading to her dismissal from the CIA and her arrest for murdering El Sueño. She expresses no regrets in doing so, fearing that El Sueño would become a dictator with the United States’ backing. If the Ghosts have fully dismantled the cartel and have taken down others involved with Santa Blanca, Bowman takes El Sueño into protective custody. El Sueño provides further intelligence on other drug cartels, terrorist groups, and arms smugglers. Bowman predicts that when the intelligence runs out, El Sueño will either be extradited by Mexico or cut loose and start a new drug cartel, starting the cycle over again. She and the Ghosts resolve to prepare themselves for the next fight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Phantom Cluster</name></author><summary type="html">Tom Clancy’s Ghost Recon Wildlands Developer(s) Ubisoft Paris Publisher(s) Ubisoft</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://phantom-cluster.github.io/assets/img/GRWL.jpg" /></entry></feed>